The chessboard shimmered not wood, but polished apple skin,
red and green squares glinting. Checkmate. The apple kingdom
crumbled, succumbing to the tart queen's strategic brilliance.
The board rizet ready for another sweet and sour battle.
King Apple, a plump fugee with a toothpick crown,
surveyed his candied fruit army. Across the board, Queen Granny Smith,
tart and strategic, adjusted her leafy headdress.
Pawn pair soldiers advanced, their sweet scent filling the
air. King Apple sacrificed a brave gala knight, a noble
crunch echoing. Granny Smith countered with a caramel
rook, trapping a citrus bishop. The tension was palpable.
A cherry balm bishop exploded near King Apple,
leaving a sticky mess. In a final gambit, Queen Granny Smith
moved.